Lim Kuang Tar

Singapore

Portfolio 🖨

% +(65)80585320

□ buddy.tlimk@gmail.com

in LinkedIn

SUMMARY

Web developer currently based in Singapore with 2.5 years of working experience with interest in building WebGL based web application. Experienced in building, maintaining and optimizing web applications primarily using React.js and Nodejs in an Agile development environment.

EDUCATION

MULTIMEDIA UNIVERSITY CYBERJAYA

June 2017 - June 2020

Bachelor of Computer Science (Hons.) - specializing Game Development

WORK EXPERIENCE

REDSQUARE SOFTWARE, Software Associate / Mid Front-end Developer

May 2021 - September 2022

- Developed up to 3 web applications projects over for the organization under an Agile environment
- Developed and implemented over 90+ responsive screens based on user interface design using React and frameworks such as NextJS and Redux for an automotive news web platform over the course of 6 months
- Trained and mentored 3 junior front-end developers for the project
- Participated in daily standups to receive tasks and coordinate with as much as 4 other project members to achieve weekly goals
- Performed troubleshooting, debugging and performance testing to improve and optimize where a web platform load time is reduced from 15 seconds to 5 seconds

SHARED EXPERIENCE ART MACHINE LLC, Web-cum-UX Developer

March 2020 - May 2021

- Communicated with the project members to design, develop over 30+ API components and deliver features for an in-house web platform
- Solved 20+ UI/UX issues with Designer with regards to the architecture and technical feasibility of the platform
- Worked with CEO to analyze 5+ automated UI testing solutions to implement and reach development needs

ACCENTURE SOLUTIONS, Intern

March 2019 - June 2019

- Maintained reliability of technical concepts documentation in a fast-paced environment resulting in time saved for the Technical Team
- Analyzed the as-is processes from users with the Functional Team for the development of the platform to optimize workflows
- Produced an infographics video to be shown and viewed by 30,000 people in client's in-house software

TECHNICAL SKILLS AND LANGUAGES

TECHNICAL SKILLS

NextJS • React.js

HTML

Git / GitHub • Figma

Javascript

Webpack

CSS

Express • Redux

Typescript

ES6

GraphQL

Docker • Node.js

LANGUAGES

• Fluent in English and Malay, both oral and written. Able to communicate using basic Mandarin

CERTIFICATIONS & EXTRACURRICULARS

EXTRACURRICULARS

CERTIFICATIONS

- Event Director for Putrajava Street Jam 2019
- Event Manager for IQI Parkour Malaysia Jam 2018
- Obstacle advisor for the first ever parkour park in Malaysia @ Johor International Youth Hub

• ADAPT Level 1 Parkour Coaching Certification